Did you give the flash drive
to the police?
I'm sure that woman
and her friends killed Ramon.
Just promise me that no one
will find out about this.
But it's broken.
I have someone I can go
to restore it.
Once you fix that,
there's more to come.
Your father was worried
because he thought our enemies
were conspiring with the police.
Don't worry about us anymore.
Just don't come running to me
asking for my help.
When the truth comes out,
everyone will know
that father got setup.
Maybe Golda was just
an accomplice.
This is a surprise inspection!
If I kill Delgado now,
what, there will be another
investigation?
Especially since it's inside
the precinct!
There's evidence against you.
That's not mine. It was a setup.
Why are you hiding this?
That's the only way I can
find out who did this.
Diego is Parak.
But he's the one the notebook
is pointing to.
"Bulalakaw," that's the firing
range where Diego and I go.
And the gun that was found
in my car,
he could have planted it.
Just follow the orders,
otherwise, Berdugo
will kill you.
Stop calling your godfather.
Maybe he's working.
I just want to get an update
about that flash drive.
Arms, please.
Sir, frisking.
Sir, clear!
I granted your request,
but don't break my trust.
Thank you, Chief.
Why do we have to talk here?
Why do you seem nervous?
What's that for?
For your protection here.
Hide it.
Protection?
Yes.
Who's going to kill me?
I was thinking,
you're going to do it, Diego.
Thank you.
Hon...
- Hi, Hon. How was your workout?
- Okay.
Is there any bad news?
Nothing.
Yvette.
You're so fast.
Is there a problem?
Actually, I have good news
for you.
Mommy's medicine seems
to be effective
because she's in a good mood
now.
That's great, I guess.
Yeah.
It's a good thing that
I'm just around the area.
You were in Bolagos?
Where?
At the precinct.
What are you doing there?
Talking to Delgado.
But why?
I don't need that.
Please, Miguel.
Don't joke like that.
What? Don't you want it?
You know, it's risky.
I might get in trouble
with that.
Like what happened to my car,
where they found a gun.
You know, Buddy,
only you can do that.
Do you know what you're saying,
Miguel?
Can you hear yourself now, Dude?
Yes.
I've noticed the change in you.
The way you dress,
your watch,
and your car.
You're such a big shot now,
Diego.
Who pays you now?
Are you also a puppet
of the syndicates?
I was hoping Delgado
would talk, and finally,
get a confession out of him...
but he didn't.
He's still playing hard to get.
Given the depth of Delgado's
involvement, he wouldn't talk.
And remember, he's a cop.
He knows all the tricks.
Maybe.
If I were you,
I'd focus on something else.
Delgado's case is old news.
Don't waste your time on him.
He's in jail.
His story is over.
Let's see.
Anyway, I'll talk to mom.
Okay.
Why do you look at me like
that now, Miguel?
We've been together
for a long time, Buddy.
What? Because of the one who's
helping you from the outside?
Who?
That Golda?
Miguel, are you going
to believe her more than me?
Well, she's just lying.
You talk as if you know Golda
very well.
Be honest with me.
Are you a true friend?
Tell me the truth.
I reminded Parak of your order
to kill Delgado.
Good.
He seemed to object.
It seems he didn't want
to do it.
But I reminded him that he would
be dead if he didn't do it.
I know he will.
I trust Diego.
He's never let us down.
What?
Are you going to kill me?
Go ahead.
Prove to me that you're
a useless cop
and a useless friend.
Miguel...
I've done everything
I can to protect you.
Now, if you don't want to accept
this help I'm giving you,
there's nothing I can do,
Miguel.
Remember, I warned you.
Be careful here.
It's you who should be careful.
If it's the devil
you're serving,
they'll drag you to hell too.
Joey.
Your phone.
You might forget it.
Thank you.
I just really want to talk
to godfather in person
about the flash drive.
Hey.
You ready?
Ready for what?
I'm going with you.
I'm your bodyguard.
I'll go where you go.
Jin Ho, no need.
I insist.
Somebody might attack you.
I have to be there.
Okay, fine.
In that case, I'll go too!
I will join too.
No need.
I can protect Joey on my own.
If you insist, I insist too.
Hey, you'll just get in the way,
Peter.
Just stay here.
Joey trusts me more than you,
right?
So just take me with you.
- Not him.
- It's not about the trust.
I'm more skilled than you are.
Can you guys please stop?
I've fixed it, Sir.
I've retrieved it.
Okay, okay.
Here, Sir.
There's just one video, Sir.
That's fine. Watch it first.
What are we going to do here,
Sir?
Well, transfer it to a new
flash drive first,
and then throw away the old one,
okay?
Okay.
Okay, okay.
Better yet, I'll just call
godfather.
Hey, do that later.
You can do that later.
- Have a snack first. Go ahead.
- Okay, Sir.
Hello?
Joey...
Hello, Godfather.
I'm sorry.
I was planning to call you,
you just beat me to it.
Regarding the flash drive
you gave me,
I was going to let you know.
How was it?
Has the flash drive
been restored?
No, my child.
I've been to three experts.
They really can't restore
the flash drive.
They said the damage
is too much.
I'm sorry, Joey.
Is that so?
Okay. Thank you for trying,
Godfather.
But, Joey...
remember, it's not because
we didn't do anything today,
you're going to get discouraged.
We can't control everything.
Okay.
Thank you anyway.
Bye, Godfather.
Hey, customer,
buy some empanadas.
Give me a dozen, hurry.
I'm sorry.
I'll just buy two pieces.
My husband and daughter
are not living with me anymore.
You only bought two pieces.
Yes, because it's just me
in my house.
- Here you go.
- Oh, right.
Okay. Where are you going now?
To the market to shop.
- Thank you. Take care.
- Thank you. See you tomorrow!
Miss, what's happening?
There's a feeding program there,
Ma'am.
- Okay, thank you.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
- Enjoy.
Don't be shy. Just eat.
Thank you.
Miss, here's some food.
Where's my comb?
Who took my comb?
- You must be the one, right?
- Oh, no, not me.
You took my comb!
No, Miss. Just calm down.
Miss, give me back my comb.
Give me back my comb!
- No.
- Give me back my comb!
- It's not me.
- Wait, wait...
- Thieves!
- I'll borrow this first.
- Give me back my comb!
- Let me take care of this.
- You're all thieves!
- Thieves!
- No, let me do it.
- My comb!
- Miss...
Miss, it's okay.
We'll find your comb.
Let's find your comb.
- My comb.
- Sit down first.
We will find your comb.
- Promise?
- Hush now. Yes, yes.
What now? How can we help
father now?
I just want to get our problem
solved
so we can be complete again.
But what are we going to do?
Maybe...
there's something I can do
to help.
Hey, the best thing that you
can do is to catch Theresa.
Find a way to make her confess
to the police!
But the only lead that I have
is Joey's video.
This guy is useless.
What kind of an agent are you?
You're useless!
You're worthless!
Then what do you call yourself?
You can't even do anything.
Yeah.
But you're the expert here,
not me!
And you can't even help Joey!
Sorry.
Oh, my, Ma'am, you have a wound.
Do you have a first aid kit?
Ma'am, sit down here.
Thank you.
Just a moment.
Why is Delgado still alive?
And lately, we've been having a
hard time contacting you, Parak.
I've just been busy, but I've
fixed the hit for Delgado.
I've already spoken to someone
who will do that.
Are you sure?
Maybe it'll take another week.
Berdugo is growing impatient.
I know. Why?
Who said I wouldn't do what
you're asking me to do?
Didn't I say I would?
So stop nagging me!
You know, I'm starting to doubt
Parak's actions.
Oh, come on.
You're just jealous.
What?
Why would I be jealous?
Because you know that there
is a possibility
that Parak will take your
position from Berdugo,
as well as here in our group.
That won't happen,
especially since Parak seems
to be hiding something.
I'll take care of him.
There you go, it's done.
Thank you.
Clarissa.
I'm Yvette.
Hello.
Thank you for what you did
earlier.
Not what you did to me,
not that.
But what you did to that woman.
Where did you learn that?
I trained in the psych ward
as a nurse.
But I didn't push through
with it
because I got married
and had a child.
That's why I focused
on my family.
Too bad.
You're so skilled.
But, well, being a full-time
housewife is also fulfilling.
Yes, but now, my husband
and daughter are busy,
so I'm home alone.
It's sad too.
Do you want to be busy again?
You know, we have an upcoming
medical mission
at our foundation.
You might want to practice
what you've learned again.
We need more volunteers.
And you'll learn a lot at our
foundation if you join us.
What? Are you up for it?
Aida, Aida...
Give me a brochure.
There, here you go.
Read it.
Okay.
Think about it.
I can't believe
I'm moving again.
It's up to you!
If you like to stay
in that place
where there's leaking water
from the ceiling, then go!
So I don't have to share a room
with anyone!
Joey...
are you okay?
You know it's a good thing
that grandmother
has another boarding house,
right?
So we can at least be
comfortable
while the other one is being
renovated, right?
So, Mom...
How do you feel
about your new meds?
I feel much, much better
than I have in months.
They said my meds are new.
So, I like it.
I see that, actually.
- Really?
- Yeah. I see that you're...
Careful.
I see that you're happier.
Hopefully, happy enough
to give your son some advice?
Okay.
Speak up.
How can you earn someone's
trust?
First question,
are you still a villain?
What do you mean, Mom?
Because when you were young,
you were always contradicting.
You always wanted to be right.
Now, my question is...
would you trust someone
if they always oppose you?
Well...
it depends.
How can someone trust you
if you don't correct them?
Trust is based on truth, right?
Trust is based on feelings.
Yes, Andrew.
You have to win someone's heart
first to make them trust you.
You have to win their heart,
and not always contradict them.
When you win their trust,
that's when you make them
see your truth.
How are we going
to be together again?
I miss us being complete.
Father, I'll give you this!
This is the evidence
that will clear your name!
Wait a minute! It's really here!
Where is it?
I have evidence!
You can't take my father!
Is he really a hero,
or is he also a member
of the syndicate?
It's Golda...
Did you write this?
I don't understand.
What does that mean?
Joey, Joey!
Joey!
We will take care of your stuff
from the other dorm.
Oppa and I will carry
your things.
We will?
Yes.
Okay.
I'll just get food
for all of us.
- I'll go outside.
- I'll come with you.
Let's go eat.
Me too!
We'll finish the transfer later.
Let's eat first.
Okay, but can you change first?
Wear something presentable.
And, I want to try a new place,
but it's a bit far from here.
Can we use your car?
It's good that you agreed
to let us come with you.
I'm thinking of taking it back.
You're so slow.
Get dressed, and get your keys.
Hurry up!
- Okay, just wait.
- Okay, I will change.
Jin Ho, get your car.
Andrew?
Andrew!
JoeyOnDuty?
What are you doing here?
Boss Budol...
I mean, Andrew.
I know...
you told me to stay away
from you...
and I said a lot of unkind
things to you,
besides telling you
to leave me alone.
But I need your help.
Help for what?
I need to find Golda.
What if he doesn't want to do
what you're making him do?
That's the payment for the sins
I've committed against you.
I did everything to protect
your husband.
Parak can't fight the group.
He knows better than
to fight us.
I know why Parak can't seem
to eliminate Delgado.
We're looking for Joey.
She left a while ago.
Maybe she just wants
to leave alone.
I asked Andrew
to help me find Golda.
Why doesn't she seem to be
coming back?
Looks like someone's
already there.
I think Golda's there.
Your happy days are over, Parak.
This is what he's using.
Do you know him, Father?
Who?